premieredate.tv 2017-06-06

# PremiereDate.News Privacy Policy - PremiereDate.TV

PremiereDate.News cares about your privacy and the information you submit and share on our website is thoroughly protected. We collect information to help improve our services, starting with subscriptions to updates and newsletters to more complex functions. For example, we inform you about all status changes with regards to each individual television series. 

**We gather information from the following sources:**

User submitted information. In order to be able to use most of our services, you must register on the website. When you create an account on PremiereDate.News, we ask you to provide us with your name and e-mail address that are both stored in your account. You can delete your account or unsubscribe from any e-mail notifications at any time. 

**Cookie files and similar technology**

To make sure our subscribers don’t have to login every time they visit the website, we use a variety of technologies, such as utilizing cookie files and similar technology. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as My TV Shows and browsing preferences.

**Protection of personal information**

PremiereDate.News shall not disclose any personal information received from users. All personal information is stored in our secure database on the website’s server. Access to the server is securely protected by a password, which is only known by the website’s administrator. 

**Does PremiereDate.News share information with third parties?**

PremiereDate.News does not share your personal information with any third parties, with the following exceptions: 

  * In order to fulfill user obligations, and only with your permission.
  * Only in accordance with the valid and applicable legal requirements.

**How to find and change your personal information**

You always have access to your personal information on your account page, which can be found here [http://premieredate.news/edit-profile.html](https://premieredate.tv/edit-profile.html). You are free to access, change, edit or delete your personal date at any time. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**

PremiereDate.News may occasionally update its privacy policy. The changes will be reflected on this page and we encourage our users to regularly check this page for any amendments or updates to our privacy policy. Your continued use of this website after any changes will constitute acceptance of such change.

**Still have concerns?**

If you still have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, you can e-mail the website’s administrator at [saynez@gmail.com](mailto:saynez@gmail.com)
